[{"answer": "Hi, Doug.  Come on in to my office", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Thank you, Ms. Giles.  Do you mind if I record our interview", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 14, "question": "Hi, Doug.  Come on in to my office", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " No, sure.  Go ahead", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Thank you, Ms. Giles.  Do you mind if I record our interview", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Thank you for meeting with me today.  I appreciate you consenting to thi", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 16, "question": " No, sure.  Go ahead", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Youre welcome.  Im happy to talk to you", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Thank you for meeting with me today.  I appreciate you consenting to thi", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Well, first of all, can you state your name and title and tell me a little bit abou", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Youre welcome.  Im happy to talk to you", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Sure.  My name is Heather Giles and Im the Director of International Studen", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 25, "question": " Well, first of all, can you state your name and title and tell me a little bit abou", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " Can you answer some questions about international students in the Unite", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Sure.  My name is Heather Giles and Im the Director of International Studen", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Sure", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Can you answer some questions about international students in the Unite", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": "How many international students are here studying in the U.S.", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Sure", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Well, we review a report called the Open Doors Report each year.  Thi", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 41, "question": "How many international students are here studying in the U.S.", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Wow!  Thats a lot!  Over half a million", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Well, we review a report called the Open Doors Report each year.  Thi", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Thats right", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Wow!  Thats a lot!  Over half a million", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Do you know what most of them study", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Thats right", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " The top three fields of study of international students are Business", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Do you know what most of them study", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " OK.  What about countries of origin?  Where do most international student", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 55, "question": " The top three fields of study of international students are Business", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Most of the international students in the US come from India, China, an", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 57, "question": " OK.  What about countries of origin?  Where do most international student", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Do they come from other countries too", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Most of the international students in the US come from India, China, an", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Sure.  They come from all corners of the world, but those are the top thre", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Do they come from other countries too", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": "Where do most of them study", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Sure.  They come from all corners of the world, but those are the top thre", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " The most popular schools that have the most international students are th", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 69, "question": "Where do most of them study", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " All right.  And what degree do most of them come to get", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 74, "question": " The most popular schools that have the most international students are th", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " Thats interesting.  Most international students, over 259,000 of them, come t", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 75, "question": " All right.  And what degree do most of them come to get", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " I didnt realize that.  I thought most of them were here getting undergra", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 83, "question": " Thats interesting.  Most international students, over 259,000 of them, come t", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " Nope.  Most come for advanced graduate study", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 89, "question": " I didnt realize that.  I thought most of them were here getting undergra", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " Do the international students at our school reflect the national statistics that yo", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Nope.  Most come for advanced graduate study", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " Pretty much.  We have 1,500 international students at our university.  Most o", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 92, "question": " Do the international students at our school reflect the national statistics that yo", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " Well, I think thats all the information I need", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 97, "question": " Pretty much.  We have 1,500 international students at our university.  Most o", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 97, "question": " Well, I think thats all the information I need", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": "   Thank you so much for talking with me.  Ill send a copy of the article over a", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 98, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 97},{"answer": " Ill look forward to reading it", "docId": "06-07", "aSentId": 102, "question": "   Thank you so much for talking with me.  Ill send a copy of the article over a", "qSentId": 101}]
